const STORE =  [
    {
        question: 'When did Real Madrid first win the European Cup?',

        answers: [
            '1956',
            '1960',
            '1945',
            '1955'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '1956'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who scored the winner goal in the 1998 final against Juventus?',

        answers: [
            'Jose Antonio Guti',
            'Roberto Carlos',
            'Clarence Seedorf',
            'Predrag Mijatovic'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Predrag Mijatovic'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Portugese soccer player has played for both Barcelona FC and Real Madrid?',

        answers: [
            'Pepe',
            'Cristiano Ronaldo',
            'Luís Nazário Ronaldo',
            'Luis Figo'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Luis Figo'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which player has scored the most goals playing for Real Madrid?',

        answers: [
            'Raúl Gonzalez Blanco',
            'Alfredo Di Stéfano',
            'Ference Puskás',
            'Cristiano Ronaldo',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Cristiano Ronaldo'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which player became an honorary president of the club after playing for the soccer team?',

        answers: [
            'Raúl Gonzalez Blanco',
            'Alfredo Di Stéfano',
            'Ference Puskás',
            'Luís Nazário Ronaldo',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Alfredo Di Stéfano'
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the first Real Madrid's manager?",

        answers: [
            'Santiago Bernabéu Yeste',
            'Alfredo Di Stéfano',
            'Ference Puskás',
            'Arthur Johnson',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Arthur Johnson'
    },
    {
        question: "Name a player that is currently part of the team that is ranked among the Top 5 striker of all time.",

        answers: [
            'Cristiano Ronaldo',
            'Hugo Sánchez',
            'Karim Benzema',
            'Emilio Butragueño',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Karim Benzema'
    },
    {
        question: "How many Uefa Champions league titles does the madrid owns?",

        answers: [
            15,
            11,
            10,
            13,
        ],
        correctAnswer: 13
    },
    {
        question: "Which player has more professional appearances with Real Madrid?",

        answers: [
            'Cristiano Ronaldo',
            'Hugo Sánchez',
            'Marcelo',
            'Raúl Gonzalez Blanco',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Raúl Gonzalez Blanco'
    },
    {
        question: "How Many La Liga titles does Real Madrid holds?",

        answers: [
            29,
            36,
            34,
            33,
        ],
        correctAnswer: 33
    },

]
